YEONU YI

iOS Developer & Designer



A logical and creative individual with excellence in identifying and solving problems. In pursuit of a new creative environment and learning new technologies. Experienced in and outside of tech, and with an MA in design, Yeonu's strength lies in creating. A hardworking individual with an enthusiasm for collaborating within a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

iOS Developer & Designer

Yeonu Studio

01/2020 - Present

- Design and build iOS applications
- Test iOS applications and fix application bugs before the final release.
- Maintain code and atomisation of the application.
- Explore and evaluate new technologies to optimise application development.

ABAP Developer | Liquid UI developer **DBDS**

11/2017 - 06/2019

- Develop, test and document SAP Programs.
- Reduce product time by developing Liquid UI script for mobile devices.
- Reduce cost of memory and administration by developing archiving programs.
- Recognise application problems, determine solutions and make logical recommendations.

Designer

Freelance

08/2016 - 11/2017

- Freelance design projects including promotional and marketing materials, musician album cover designs, and personal digital and glass designs.

Administrator

Kookmin Uni.

04/2014 - 04/2016

CONTRACT EXPERIENCE @ DBDS

- Projects Role: Developer

Samsung Fire & Marine Insurance

09/2017 - 12/2018

GS Power

08/2018

Samsung Life Insurance

03/2018 - 05/2018

Yesco

01/2018 - 02/2018

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Development Ssangyong Institute of System Technology

03/2017 - 10/2017

MA - Ceramic Design

Kookmin Uni. Seoul, SOUTH KOREA 03/2014 - 02/2017 - 4.4 / 4.5 (equivilent to 1st)

BA - Ceramic Craft, Minor in Fashion Design

Kookmin Uni. Seoul, SOUTH KOREA 03/2009 - 02/2014 - 3.8 / 4.5 (equivilent to 2:1)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

iOS Mobile Application Development

Xcode, Swift, Objective-C, SwiftUI, CocoaPods Realm, Core Data, RESTful API, Git, GitHub

Cross Platform Mobile Development

Flutter, Dart, Android Studio

Other Programming Languages

Java, JavaScript, Oracle SQL, CSS3, JSP, JSON, HTML

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator

Licenses & Certifications

Engineer Information Processing

Human Resources Development Service of Korea

LANGUAGES







RELEASED APPS



Gonefellas Tarot

- Personal Project using Swift, Realm, JSON
- Available in App Store



Easy Peasy Currency

- Using Swift, API, Core Data, JSON
- Available in App Store